Jung Hoo Lee
>> Jung Hoo Lee hit a single, so he's on
first base.
>> They're getting in a fight.
>> Jersey's 165.
>> B L A B L A
>> Tonight, I'm watching the San Francisco
Giants play the LA Dodgers. They're
rivals, so I think it's going to be a
pretty intense game. It might get kind
of heated. I'm really excited to see
some big players tonight. Lee Jung Hoo,
Kim Ha Seong, and Ohtani. Oracle Park in
San Francisco is known as being one of
the most beautiful stadiums in the US.
You can literally hit a home run into
the ocean. I heard that some fans
actually sit in kayaks waiting for home
run balls to be hit to them. The game
just started, so let's watch and have
fun tonight.
I'm rooting for the Giants because
they're the home team and Busan has the
same mascot, Lotte Giants.
>> Jung Hoo Lee, runners at first and
third, one out.
He wraps one.
And it's going to be
two out.
>> It's the top of the second inning and
we're up by three. The Dodgers are at
bat, so I'm going to go grab a bite to
eat [music] quick.
Two iconic spots in the stadium are this
giant baseball glove and this Coca-Cola
bottle, which is actually a slide. I
want to go down it, but they have it
closed [music] off right now. Bummer.
I'm at the merch table. I want to buy an
Lee Jung Hoo uniform. Excuse me, do you
Do you other Lee Jung Hoo merch besides
the jersey? Like a hat or anything like
that?
>> We have a t-shirt.
>> T-shirt? Just like a giant shirt with
his name on the back?
>> It's Ohtani versus Jung Hoo Lee.
>> Ohtani? Ah,
oh that's pretty good though, too. How
much is a jersey like that?
>> Jerseys are 165.
>> 165. What do you think?
>> Yeah, today's shirt is 40.
>> 40? Okay. All right, I'm going to do one
of the black t-shirts, please. What size
is hanging up there?
>> Should be a small or medium.
>> That should be all right. Medium,
probably. Is it like 100% cotton? It
might shrink.
>> Yeah.
It is 100% cotton.
>> So it's going to shrink, probably,
right? I'll go for a medium.
>> Have a wonderful day.
>> Thank you so much.
I wanted a jersey, but it was a little
too expensive. So I settled for a
t-shirt.
Isn't it obvious? Jung Hoo Lee, the This
is the perfect way to remember tonight.
Hello. One crab sandwich, [music]
please. Thank you so much.
This crab sandwich was $30. It better be
good or I'm going to be mad. I usually
go for a classic hot dog at ball games,
but I heard this crab sandwich is not to
be missed at Oracle Park. So, let's try
it.
Mmm.
I'm not a huge seafood fan, but this is
really good. This does not taste like
stadium food. It tastes pretty gourmet,
actually.
>> Worth 30 bucks?
>> I'm going to say it's worth 30 bucks for
stadium food.
Hello. Can I please get one order of the
chicken tenders with garlic fries? One
Coke Zero, as well, please.
>> Okay, what size would you like? We have
a medium and we also have a large.
>> Medium should be fine. Yeah.
Oh, fresh, eh? Thank you.
>> And you do have your napkins and
everything in the back.
>> Okay. Do you have a lid for this?
No lids? Okay. Okay.
>> Sorry.
>> It's all right. Taste
These fries are fresh, crunchy, and
super garlicky. Worth the wait.
>> How much?
>> 30-something.
It's a much bigger portion than the crab
sandwich, though.
Thank you.
This is our luck. We bring the rain
every time, without fail. It's pouring.
>> [cheering]
>> Jung Ho Lee hit a single, so he's on
first base. I see so many people here
wearing his jersey. Lots of fans of him
at this stadium.
>> [cheering and applause]
[cheering]
>> We almost got another run, but the ump
called him out. Bummer. Fun fact, I used
to be an ump as a part-time job. It was
fun, but also lots of pressure. Not an
easy job.
All the fans are talking trash over
there. They're getting in a fight.
>> [cheering]
>> I don't care if I never get back, cuz
it's me.
Do you know that song? No? It's a
classic baseball song. Every American
knows it.
I love the fan cam. It's so fun watching
people dancing and just having a good
time.
It's Nori bonding at the stadium
tonight.
>> [cheering]
>> The pitcher's throwing strikes.
>> Two down, THE PITCH. SWING AND A MISS,
HE STRUCK HIM OUT.
HE BLEW A FAST
>> THE GIANTS JUST WON three to one. Let's
try to hurry up and beat the crowd. We
got to grab an Uber.
Everyone's running for the exit. [music]
Everybody calm down. Take a deep breath.
It took too long to get an Uber, so I
got a Waymo instead, which is a
driverless taxi. It's kind of freaky,
but pretty cool. They're all over the
streets of San Francisco.
I just got home and had to try on my new
shirt right away. How's it look, guys?
Baseball [music] is my favorite sport,
so that was lots of fun. Actually, I
played softball for a large part of my
life and I was a first baseman. I don't
want to brag, but [music] my nickname
used to be the magnet. I hope you had
fun watching the game with me and I'll
see you next [music] time. Bye.